http://jocsoft.com/privacy.htm

Youtube Downloader | Youtube to iPod | Youtube to iPhone | Youtube Download | Youtube Converter | Youtube to PSPHomeDownloadPurchaseAffiliatesSupportPrivacy StatementIt is Jocsoft.com policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and e-mail address or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the information (such as to reply to your request or to handle your complaint). Personal information will not be released to third parties except to further the purpose for which you provide the information, or if release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings. There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties. Our server is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information about its visitors.
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. Jocsoft.com has no control over the information collected by sites that it is linked to and cannot take responsibility for those sites actions. Youtube DownloaderYoutube DownloaderYoutube to iPod ConverterYoutube to iPhone ConverterYoutube to PSP ConverterYoutube FLV DownloaderYoutube Download StudioYoutube MP3 DownloaderVideo ConverterFLV ConverteriPod Video ConverteriPhone Video ConverterPSP Video ConverterZune Video Converter3GP Video ConverterMP4 Video ConverterJocsoft Video ConverterOther SoftwareTopNotesJOC Web FinderDVD File PrinterJOC Web SpiderJOC Email CheckerJOC Master ShutdownHomeYoutube to iPod Converter | Youtube to iPhone Converter | Youtube to PSP Converter |Youtube Download Studio | Youtube Converter | TopNotes | JOC Web Finder | DVD File Printer | JOC Web Spider | JOC Email Checker | JOC Master Shutdown | JOC Print Commander | JOC CalcJOC Menu | JOC Screen Designer | LinksPad Files | Y2K Statement | Terms | Privacy Policy | SupportAll product names are trademarks of their respective owners. Copyright © 2012 Jocsoft.com - Youtube Download Studio
